https://www.newsfeeds.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy and Disclaimer
Newsfeeds.com is a Usenet and VPN Package review website. The content on this website is the opinion of Newsfeeds.com.
.
Do we use cookies?
No, we do not use cookies.
3rd Parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Disclosure
The experience and benefit we have received from using a  service is typical and is dependant on many other factors that may influence other people’s experience and benefit from using the product or service.
Best Bargain Usenet
1
2
3
4
5
